transglobalexpress.co.uk 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy and Other Information | Transglobal Express

Transglobal Express is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe that it is important you know how we treat the information about you that we receive on the Internet.

## Information Collected

In general, you may visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Our servers collect the domain names, operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and browser (e.g., Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Internet Explorer). This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. Transglobal Express uses this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information such as first and last name, telephone number, and other similar information are known only when voluntarily provided by a visitor for registration or other participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities.

## Use Of Your Information

We may use the personal information you provide for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of our Site and make improvements; (2) to respond to specific requests from visitors; (3) to protect the security or integrity of our Site when necessary; (4) to send you notices and solicitations regarding Site and our businesses; and (5) in general to promote and market products to you. These solicitations may take the form of mailings or other couriers, telephone calls, e-mail solicitations and other methods of contact. If you do not want to receive these solicitations from us using your personally identifiable information, please notify us. At times, we may conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect the information from you on the Internet.

## Disclosure of Information

Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this Site is retained by Transglobal Express. Transglobal Express do not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this personally identifiable information outside this company, except where disclosure is required by law.

## Other Websites

This Site may contain links to other sites of third parties. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for checking this policy when you visit our Site to review the current policy. If you do not agree with the policy, you should cease use of the Site immediately.

## Cookies

A technology called ‘cookies’ may be used to provide you with tailored information. A ‘cookie’ is a tiny element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Our cookies collect the operating system and browser that a visitor is using.

## Telephone Calls

We record all telephone calls for the protection of our customers and our staff. All calls to our 0845 145 1212 are charged at your local network rate.

## Access Rights

You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. Please write to us at the following address to obtain a copy of the personal information Transglobal Express holds about you:  
Transglobal Express, Unit 5, The Gateway, Wirral International Business Park,  Bromborough, Wirral CH62 3NX
